-来了  -来了
- Hey, man. - Hey, man.
-你给我带了咖啡  -对
- You brought me coffee? - Yeah.
我记得你上一次给我带咖啡
You realize, I think the last time you brought me coffee,
我们还在同一组里
we were riding in a squad together.
返璞归真挺好的
Well, return to basics is good.
是吗
That right?
我觉得我们都不会怀念你的糊咖啡
I didn't realize either one of us missed your burnt coffee.
到底怎么回事  老埃
What the hell's is going on, Al?
缉毒队的特里昨晚给我打电话
Terry from Narcotics called me last night.
鲁本·吉尔布莱特私藏毒品的指控不成立
Ruben Gilbright's possession charge was dropped.
所以
So...
我的计划不管用
My plan didn't work.
伍兹在保护他
Woods is protecting him.
想确保他能作证指控我
Wants to make sure he can testify against me.
好吧
All right.
如果内务部来找你
If Internal Affairs is gonna show up on my door with, uh--
-有逮捕令的话...   -阿尔  我不会
- an arrest warrant-- - Al, I'm not gonna--
不会让事情发展到那一步的
I'm not gonna let it get that far.
你必须那么做
Yes, you are.
为了我们两个
For both our sakes, yes, you are.
汉克  我们静等风来
Hank, we let it come.
因为他们不会罢休的
Because in the end, they won't have enough.
所以就把我推出去吧
So we let it hit me.
由我解决  直面地狱
I go through it. Deal with the hell.
然后我们再重生
And we come out the other side.
这是唯一能拯救我们的办法
That's the way we both get saved here.
好吗
Okay?
老大
Boss.
我在助理检察官办公室的线人
All right, so my contact in the ASA's office
下午之前都会在法庭上
is in court until this afternoon.
她一出来我们就能知道结果
As soon as she's out, I'll have answers.
如果有动作  她会知道的
If it's on the move, she'll know about it.
听着  我不只要结论
Listen, I need more than just confirmation.
要想解决这件事  我需要所有细节  明白吗
I need details if I'm gonna outrun this, okay?
明白
Copy that, yeah.
好  不要让别人知道是我的意思
All right, no one can know it came from me.
-当然了  -汉克
- No, of course. - Hank.
-怎么  -刚刚有一个小姑娘找你
- Yeah? - A teenage girl was just here
说她名叫汉娜
looking for you. Said her name was Hannah.
-汉娜  -对  我说让她等等
- Hannah? - Yeah, I tried to get her
我打电话找你  但她说等不了
to stick around while I called you but she said she couldn't.
然后就跑了  留了这个给你
She ran out of here and left you that.
-谢谢  -没事
- Thanks. - Okay.
芝加哥警署
亨利·博伊特  反黑组
诺贝尔北街36号
你说过我可以来找你帮忙  汉娜·凯兹
你还好吗  老大
You okay, boss?
没事
Yeah.
走  我们出去一趟
Come on, let's take a ride.
汉娜·凯兹  无前科
Hannah Cates, no priors.
最后地址是几年前留下的
Last known address is from a few years ago.
西郊的公寓  这是她的...
Apartment in West Clearing. This is her...
-对  -现在18岁了
- Yeah. - Yeah, she's 18 now.
汉娜·凯兹
你把你的名片给了一个孩子
This is a kid you gave your card to?
只是我碰到的一个孩子
No, it's just a kid I met.
很久以前的事了
I mean, a long time ago.
她卷入什么事件了吗
She involved in anything?
从来没有
No, never was.
好  就是这里
All right, this is the place.
我进去  你在外面
I'll take inside, you take out.
如果她不在  我就给你20元
If she's not there, I'll give you 20.
-我们就回去  -好的  老大
- Then we'll call it. - Sounds good, boss.
亚当  我看到她了  你等着
Adam, I got her in sight. Hang tight.
-明白  -汉娜
- Copy that. - Hannah?
坐
Here, have a seat.
你不想点咖啡吗
Sure you don't want any coffee?
-对  -早餐呢
- Yeah. - Breakfast?
-这里的蛋不错  -我不需要
- Got good eggs here. - No, I can't.
不用了  谢谢
I'm good. Thanks.
怎么了
What's going on?
我只是好奇
I was just wondering
如果我需要帮助的话
what would happen if...
会怎么样呀
if I needed help.
我会帮助你
Then I would help you.
我很抱歉
Listen, I'm sorry.
我知道我们很久没见了  我...
I mean, I know it's been a while, I--
没关系
That's okay.
你没欠我什么
You never owed me anything.
我阿姨告诉我了
My aunt told me what happened.
你儿子的事
With your son.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你一定很心碎
It must have broke you.
无论什么事
Whatever it is...
我们都能解决的
We can work it out.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我会帮助你
I'm gonna help you.
翻译     小酸奶   西之   不高兴童鞋   小萝莉
我想我可以吃点蛋
Guess I could eat some eggs.
很好  那我们点吧  好吗
Okay, good, let's do that. Okay?
翻译     Lynn_宁   H小欠
我得先去趟卫生间
I just need to run to the bathroom first,
校对     小酸奶   圈圈
-然后再点好吗  -好的
- and then we can order? - Sure.
-好  -去吧
- Okay. - Okay.
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
后期     8T
总监     圈圈
-要菜单吗  -对
- Some menus? - Yeah.
借过
Excuse me.
鲁兹  注意前门
Ruz, keep an anchor down out front.
我在前门
Yeah, I'm here.
-一切正常吗  -不  她跑了
- All good? - No, she bolted.
好吧  注意看
All right, keep your eyes open.
灰色连帽上衣  蓝色牛仔裤
Grey hoodie, blue jeans.
我看到她了
I got her.
在小巷子向东走
She's heading east in the alley.
汉娜
Hannah! Hey!
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第二十集
5021紧急情况  我们在追一辆
5021 Emergency Squad, we are in pursuit
银色本田巡游者
of a silver Toyota Land Cruiser.
最后一次见到是往南驶往诺贝尔路和哈伯德路
Last seen headed southbound on Noble and Hubbard.
速度很快
High rate of speed.
部分车牌号842
Partial plate: 8-4-2.
袭击者很可能施行了绑架
Offenders wanted for possible aggravated kidnapping.
一名西班牙裔男性  持械  司机是白人
One male, Hispanic, armed. White male driver.
老大  怎么回事
Boss, what the hell is going on here?
收到  5021小队
Copy that, 5021 squad.
警长  根据车牌号  我们搜到了112个结果
Sarge, we have 112 hits on that partial plate.
我们正在排查找
We're sorting through them looking for one registered
巡游者
to a Land Cruiser.
海莉正在调取交通录像
Hailey's accessing the traffic cams,
但我们还没找到汉娜
but we don't have a bead on Hannah.
她名下没有注册手机号码
Now, she doesn't have a cell phone registered to her
所以我无法通过紧急定位找她...
so I can't do an emergency ping--
金  最新款银色巡游者
Kim. Late model silver Land Cruiser
部分牌照号842  六分钟前驶过
partial plate: 8-4-2, passed a traffic camera
16街和国道交叉口的摄像头
six minutes ago, 16th and State.
海莉  我们没看到  直升机看到
Hailey, we don't have them. Did the eye in the sky
-他们驶过16街了吗  -正在核查
- get them past 16th? - Checking.
后面  后面  后面
Behind, behind, behind.
5021I  听到16街和国道之间有枪声
5021 Ida, we got shots fired at 16th and State.
建议便衣警官出警响应
Be advised: plainclothes officers responding.
收到  5021I
Copy that, 5021 Ida.
5021I  这些枪声来自
5021 Ida, those shots fired are coming from
南1600街区的北席勒信用合作社
the South 1600 block, North Schiller Credit Union.
锁上了
It's locked.
上
Go.
-鲁塞克  你没事吧  -我没事  趴下
- Ruzek, you okay? - I'm good. Stay down.
呼叫指挥中心  有人持枪袭警
10-1, 10-1, we got shots fired at the police.
北席勒信用合作社有一伙
We got a bona fide robbery happening
持械抢劫犯
at North Schiller Credit Union.
有枪
Gun!
快走
Go!
5021  巡游者往18街逃窜
5021, Land Cruiser fleeing southbound towards 18th street.
YDH842
Young, David, Henry, 8-4-2.
好了  冷静点
All right, just stay calm.
继续压住  好吗
Keep pressure right there, all right?
准备好了吗  会很疼
You ready? This is gonna hurt.
给我叫辆救护车  1656南国道
Get me an ambulance. 1656 South State Street.
收到
Copy that.
海莉  我们要帮助抢劫凶案组破这个案子吗
Hailey, we backing up Robbery Homicide on this?
不  我们接手了  事件发生的时候
No, we're taking it. Voight and Ruzek were here
博伊特和鲁塞克在场  这就发生在绑架之后
when it kicked off. It was on the heels of an abduction.
好了  汉娜·凯兹  18岁
All right, Hannah Cates. She's 18.
今天早上在我桌上留下了我的名片和一张字条
Left my card and a note at the front desk this morning,
需要帮助  我见了她  她跑了
wanted help, I met her. She bolted.
在咖啡店外被人抓走了
And was grabbed right outside the coffee shop.
陌生人绑架作案吗
Stranger abduction?
感觉她好像认识这些人
It felt like she knew these guys.
那汉娜在劫案期间在哪里
So, where was Hannah during the robbery?
被绑在车后座上
Tied up in the backseat, trunk.
送到另一个地方了
Dropped at a second location.
我们12分钟前跟丢了那辆车
We lost eyes on that car for like 12 minutes.
那个员工已经送去医院了
Ah, the employee's on his way to Med.
子弹划伤了他的股动脉  所以...
Bullet severed his femoral, so...
目击证人说一切都发生的非常快
Witnesses say it happened quick.
信用社开门  劫犯冲进来
Credit Union opened, offenders barged inside.
不过没人说看到过一名少女  老大
No one mentioned seeing a teenage girl, though, boss.
好  海莉  去里面的现场
All right, Hailey, head up the scene inside.
我们找联调局谈谈  看看有没有
All right, let's talk to the FBI, see if this matches
类似手法的劫案
a robbery pattern.
安东尼奥  继续查汉娜
Antonio, get a bead on Hannah for me.
她的阿姨名叫安妮·凯兹
Her aunt is Anne Cates.
是她的法定监护人  但她档案上最后登记的住址
That's her legal guardian but the last known address
是无人居住的
on file is vacant.
我去查查
I'll track her down.
我在助理地检办公室的线人出法庭了
My contact in the ASA's office is out of court.
我能拖一会
I can hold off.
不  去吧
No, go now.
好的
You got it.
天啊
Oh, man.
博伊特说汉娜有他的名片  什么意思
Hey, what did Voight mean, Hannah had his card?
他的名片吗
His business card?
他就是这样的
That's his thing.
这几年发出去了不少名片
He's given out a bunch over the years.
一般都是给附近的孩子
Usually kids that grew up in rough neighborhoods.
罩着他们
Looks after them.
琳德赛十四岁的时候给了她一张
Gave one to Lindsay when she was 14.
所以她说博伊特救了她
That's why she said Voight saved her.
是吗
Yeah?
的确是他风格
That is a thing.
他们从登记处肯定抢不了多少钱
They couldn't have gotten much out of the registers.
没错  出纳说不到三千
Yeah, teller said there was less than three grand.
钱都存放在后面
Real payload was in the back.
这不是什么好兆头
Well, it's not a good sign.
这里本来应该有两名员工
They should've used both employees back here.
一名打开登记处的抽屉
One opens the registers,
另一名往后门走了
the other accesses the back door.
这样能遵守2分钟法则  减少小额票据
Helps obey the Two Minute Rule. Lessens the small bills.
他们也没必要打上八十几发子弹
They didn't need to fire 80 rounds, either.
一个失血过多的人得费好大劲
Damn hard for a man who's bleeding out
才能打开安全门
to open a security door.
我最讨厌这种抢劫杀人案
I hated ones like this in Robbery Homicide.
最残暴的凶犯  最大的伤亡
Worst crews, highest body counts.
他们根本不知道
They're the ones that don't know what the hell
自己在干什么
they're doing.
汉娜·凯兹
女性
无前科
无已知住址
要求与博伊特见面
完全检测不到弹道结果
No match on ballistics, at all.
枪支查不到  车辆是偷来的
AK's are clean, the SUV popped up stolen.
目前为止一无所获
Cold trail, so far.
我知道你看到
I know you saw a Beretta
绑架汉娜的人拿了一把手枪
on the offender who abducted Hannah.
但是他们在现场没用过
But they didn't use it at the scene.
没错  钱上也没有追踪器
Yeah, and there's no trackers.
或者染料包
Or dye packs on this money.
伊利诺伊州惩教部给我发了一系列
IDOC did send me a list of cats on parole
相同背景的假释犯名单  但是这个名单
with similar backgrounds, but we can't do anything
没什么用  警长
with this list, Sarge.
全都不在监狱里了
Nobody's staying in jail anymore.
汉娜的阿姨真是难找
Hannah's aunt is proving difficult to find.
档案中无人居住的住址是一年前搬走的
The vacant on file was cleared out a year ago.
安娜留了新的地址
Anne left a forwarding address.
我查过了  但是房东说她只来住了一个星期
I checked, but the landlord said she was only there a month.
那可不妙
Well, that's not good,
因为我们现在所有关于汉娜的信息
because every piece of paper we have on Hannah is dated
都是从那次搬家后开始的  安全保险
from that move. Health insurance,
注册的手机号  学校注册
cell phone registration, school enrollment.
安娜上次缴税缴了大概有一万四
And the last time Anne filed taxes, she made about 14 grand.
那可远远算不上穷人
That's well below the poverty line.
也许是和家里人关系不好
Probably crashing with family.
不  没有其他家人了
No, there is no other family.
安妮的哥哥  汉娜的爸爸在监狱里
Anne's brother, Hannah's dad, he's in jail.
四年前贩毒被抓了
Got busted for dealing four years ago.
你就是这么认识汉娜的
Is that how you met Hannah?
不是  我从她七岁就认识她了
No, I've known her since she was seven.
什么线索都没有
Got a whole lot of nothing.
没有DNA  他们戴的手套上也没有指纹
No DNA, and the gloves they wore gave us zero fingerprints.
他们就只按规矩干了这么一件事
About the only thing they did by the book.
后巷没人看到
We didn't have eyes in the back alley
但是有室内监控视频
but we got footage inside.
妈的
Damn.
就这些了  没有多少可查线索
That's all of it. That's not a lot to go on.
抢劫发生的12分钟前
Look, 12 minutes before that robbery,
那两个人胁迫汉娜上了车
those two men forced Hannah into a car.
原因是什么
Why?
在发现抢劫案的线索之前
Okay, until something pops on the robbery,
我们先从绑架案着手
let's start with the abduction.
找到汉娜的阿姨
So find Hannah's aunt.
她们住在哪里
Where they've been living.
接触过谁
Who have they been in contact with?
应该能查到是谁带走了她
That's gonna lead to who the hell took her.
她给你回复了吗
She give you an answer?
已经传唤了特殊大陪审团
Special Grand Jury has already been summoned.
公诉人是谁
Who's the prosecutor?
詹姆斯·欧沙
James Osha.
老大
Boss, hey...
他们会在48小时内聚齐
They're gonna convene in 48 hours.
我们没问题的
We'll be fine.
我都不知道你们是怎么跟踪到我的
I don't even understand how you guys tracked me down.
你的灵通卡注册的是这个地址
Well, your Link card is registered to this address.
看来我侄女汉娜是真出事了
Uh, so something really happened to my niece, Hannah?
我看到你们  就想你们应该是他派来的
I saw you guys and I just figured you were cops he sent.
谁派来的  什么
Cops, who sent? What?
那个警长
That sergeant.
不过汉娜已经不和我住了
But Hannah doesn't live with me anymore,
也就不用汇报情况了吧
so I guess there's no need for a check-in, huh?
汉克·博伊特警长会来询问汉娜的情况
Sergeant Hank Voight checks in on Hannah?
对  不过我说了  她不住这里
Yeah, he did, but like I said, she's not here, so...
她十八了
She's 18.
好吧
Okay.
你上次见她是什么时候
When was the last time you saw her?
我不知道  她自己过
I don't know, she's on her own.
等等  你不记得你上次见她的时间
Uh, wait, but you don't remember when you saw her last?
那她现在的住址呢
Okay, what about her current address?
她只说她找到了地方住
She just said she found a place.
没给我地址
She didn't give me an address.
安妮
Look, Anne...
如果你有什么误会  那很抱歉
I'm sorry if we miscommunicated with you,
但我们认为汉娜陷入了极大的危险之中
but we believe that Hannah's in some pretty serious danger.
如果你能给我们点信息
So, anything you can tell us...
上次你见到她  她和谁在一起
Last time you saw her, who she was with...
随便什么信息都能帮助到我们
Any of that might help us.
-任何信息  -拜托了
- Anything. - Come on.
汉娜最后跟你住是什么时候
When's the last time Hannah actually lived with you?
汉娜十八了
Hannah's 18.
他问的可不是这个
Yeah, but that's not what he asked.
我好好地照顾了那姑娘很久
Look, I took good care of that girl for a real long time.
她都不是我亲生的
She's not even my kid.
你们想通知儿童保护局吗
You wanna call Child Services?
那就通知啊  是她自己想出去住的
Go ahead. She wanted to be on her own.
她年龄够大  可以照顾好自己了
She was old enough to take care of herself.
她当时都16了
She was 16,
比我离开家的时候还大了一岁呢
a whole year older than I was when I left home.
我只知道她是搬出去和朋友住
All I know is that she left to live with her friend...
艾迪  什么桑普特
Addie. Something--Sumpter.
我之前是听说她们挤在卡纳瑞维尔的一个地方
Last I knew they were squatting somewhere in Canaryville.
差不多吧
Maybe.
行吧
Okay.
-艾迪  -警察  警察
- Hey, Addie. - Cops, cops!
-快走  -等等
- Let's move! - Hey, wait.
冷静
Calm down.
艾迪  艾迪
Addie! Addie!
别跑  行不
Come on. All right?
放轻松
Chill out.
转身  那边是你的地方吧
Okay, turn around, were you-- is that your space over there?
就这个破地方
All this destroyed area in here?
你有家当吗
You got stuff somewhere?
有没有
Yes or no?
你们不能搜查我的东西
You can't search my stuff.
事实上  这块地并不属于你  所以...
Actually, this property's not yours, so...
那你们就随便搜吧
So just have at it then.
你坐一下
Just sit down.
我们不是要逮捕你
Okay, we're not here to arrest you.
也不想逮捕你
We don't want to bring you in.
我们只是有几个关于汉娜的问题想问你
We just wanna ask you some questions about Hannah.
她住在这里吗
Okay, does she live here?
不住
She's not here.
你上次见她是什么时候
So, when was the last time you've seen her?
不记得了  抱歉
No idea, I'm sorry.
我今早见过她
Well, I saw her this morning.
然后两个持枪男子就把她推进了一辆车
Right before two guys with guns shoved her into an SUV.
然后他们就抢劫了一家信用合作社
And then they went and robbed a credit union.
一通开枪  还打死了一个人
Shot the place up. Left a guy for dead.
艾迪  她可是你最好的朋友
Addie, this is your best friend.
你知不知道她在哪里
You know where she is?
艾迪  如果你是害怕什么人或者...
Addie, if you're scared of somebody or any--
我才不怕  我是真不知道
I'm not scared. I don't know jack.
我没和她说过话
I haven't talked to Hannah.
-好吧  我们走  -等等  你不是说
- All right, come on. - Wait, I thought you said
-不抓我的吗  -我们是不想
- you weren't gonna take me in? - Well, no, we didn't want to,
可现在必须得抓你了
but now we need to.
那个女孩很害怕  但我觉得她知道什么
That girl's scared, but I feel like she knows something.
她说汉娜从没和她一起住过
She said that Hannah never lived there with her
但其他流浪者说他们在那里见过另一个女孩
but other squatters said they did see another female there
和汉娜的形象相符  但他们不记得
that matched Hannah's description, but they can't
她们身边还有没有其他男人
recall a man ever being with her.
但这不代表她们没在外面见其他男人
Right, but it doesn't mean they didn't meet men outside.
那个地方本来就是重点关注区域
Area Central's had that address flagged.
风化组每个月都会检查
And Vice has been doing routine sweeps
附近的巷子
in the adjoined alley each month.
-你觉得是皮条客  -有可能
- You're thinking pimp? - Maybe.
这些姑娘在街头已经
The truth is, these girls have been on the street
混了一年半  不少人知道她们
for a year and a half, and they've been exposed to a lot.
你自己说的汉娜看上去认识他们
You yourself said that it looked like Hannah knew 'em.
那么
So...
可能那家伙在训练培养她
It's possible that this guy was grooming her.
而她没有适应  所以她出来
And she didn't take well to it. So she stepped out,
找你帮助
went to your for help,
然后他们把她抓了回去
and then they pull her to keep her in line.
我不知道  杰
I don't know, Jay.
副业是武装抢劫的皮条客
Pimps who sideline into armed robbery--
这些家伙不是专业的银行抢劫犯
These guys are not professional bank robbers.
很明显
They made that clear.
可能是为了弄到钱什么都做
This could be "Anything for a buck."
好  艾迪呢
All right, where's Addie?
和鲁塞克一起  不说话
She's with Ruzek. Not talking.
除了说要找媒体
Except to call the media.
好吧
Okay.
和风化组打电话  所有这些都告知他们
Listen, get on the horn with Vice, run all this past them.
-关门好吗  -好
- Hey, grab the door, will ya? - Yeah.
我是 詹姆斯·欧沙  请留言
You've reached James Osha. Leave a message.
警长  附近刚发生一起抢劫案
Sarge, a robbery in progress just came over the zone.
罗根广场的货币兑换所
The hold up alarm was activated at the Currency Exchange
紧急报警器刚响了
in Logan Square.
巡逻车在路上  但报警者说
Squads are in route but the 911 caller is saying
抢劫犯蒙面并携带自动步枪
masked offenders with assault rifles.
发生了什么
What the hell happened?
一切发生得太快
Things went sideways fast.
孩子新来的  上周入职
The kid was new. Started last week.
没有后面金库的钥匙
Didn't have a key to the back vaults.
没有值班经理吗
There wasn't a manager on site?
在关门的时候抢劫一个地方
Well, you rob the place at closing.
他们可以就这么离开的  但...
They could have just left but...
两个蒙面男性劫犯  携带AK47
Two masked male offenders. AK-47s.
有三名劫犯  其中两个男性  30左右
There were three offenders. Two males, fit, 30s.
还有一名女性
And one female.
是汉娜吗
Is that Hannah?
她也参与其中了
She participated?
这案子应该马上移交到抢劫凶案组
Case should immediately be handed over to Robbery Homicide.
一开始就应该交给他们
Should have been theirs from the get.
不  整个案子是从
No. This whole case jumped off
我当班的时候目击到的
from an aggravated kidnapping
一起严重绑架案开始的
that I witnessed while on duty.
现在三个人死了  你面对的是一个
And now you've got three dead and one in critical condition
情况危急的烂摊子  汉克
to show for it, Hank.
我们已经为这个案子忙了24小时
It is not gonna serve anybody
现在把这案子从情报组移交出去
to yank this from Intelligence
对谁都不好  你懂的
when we've been knee deep in it for 24 hours, you know that.
我们查到了线索
We got leads invested.
拜托  就...
Now please, just--
让中央警局协助我们
have Area Central back us up.
好
Fine.
我要把抢劫录像和
I'm gonna get Hannah's ID out
汉娜的身份发布给媒体
with the robbery footage, state wide to the media.
丹尼  你这么做...
Danny, you do that...
最后只会让他们像九成失控的罪犯一样
This is gonna end like 90% of crime sprees do:
-酿成惨剧  -你担心激起众怒吗
- In bullets. - You worried about reform optics?
不  我是担心
No, I'm worried about
一个被胁迫的18岁女孩
an 18-year-old girl who I think is being coerced.
一个我认识的女孩
A girl I know,
她曾向我求助
who came to me for help.
丹尼  我看到了她对劫犯的反应
Denny, I saw how she reacted to the offenders.
她很怕他们  她是被掳走的
She was scared of them. They took her!
你是说她是帕蒂·赫斯特吗
You saying she's Patty Hearst?
赫斯特家族继承人  被绑架后成为著名银行劫匪
你怎么认识这女孩的
How do you even know this girl?
以前人家把我介绍给她的
Someone introduced me to her a long time ago.
我几年没和她联系了
And I haven't talked to her in a few years.
所以你没有那么了解她了
So, you don't know her that well anymore?
对吗
Right?
我要把她的身份公布出去  还有抢劫录像
I'm gonna put Hannah's ID out, with the robbery footage.
-好吗  -丹尼
- All right? - Denny...
卢戈队长让我打个电话就好
You know, Chief Lugo just told me to call.
但我觉得还是趁我能来的时候
But I figured I shouldn't waste an opportunity to come by here
过来一趟吧
while I still can.
因为你和老埃很快就会
Because pretty soon you and Al are gonna be, uh...
锒铛入狱
Tied up.
那女孩真是可惜了
Damn shame about the girl.
但你与狮子共寝
But you lay down with lions,
就会和他们一起被猎杀
you get hunted with them.
你们都在等什么
What are you all waiting for?
告诉我进展
Tell me what we got.
弹道检测和信用社劫案的相符
Um, ballistics was a match at the credit union.
我们把两处的监控视频
We went back a month in security footage
都倒回一个月进行查看  但没有发现
for both locations, nothing.
而且没有关于疑犯的报警电话
And no service calls of suspicious persons.
我查了摄像头  交通探头  交管局
I've been checking PODS, traffic cams, CTA--
目前为止没有发现  警长
nothing yet, Sarge.
但他们得从货币兑换所那儿逃掉啊
But they had to flee the Currency Exchange somehow.
艾迪那有消息吗
All right, anything new on Addie?
她还是不开口  警长
Uh, Addie ain't talking, Sarge.
她说不知道那些人
She said she don't know those guys
也不知道汉娜和他们的关系
or what the hell Hannah was doing with them.
我自己要去审这件事
All right, well I'm gonna take a run at it.
把文件整理好给我
Put a folder together for me, will ya?
把货币兑换所那儿的录像调给我看
Get that footage from the currency exchange for me.
如果艾迪不说话
You know, if Addie's not gonna talk,
只能从汉娜身上查他们的身份了
then we'll just narrow their IDs off Hannah.
她认识那些人  意味着她在哪儿见过他们
I mean, she knew these men. Means she met them somewhere.
查查她的每个住处
Check every address that she lived at,
住过的旅店
hostels she crashed in,
还有哈罗德华盛顿图书馆做暑期工的时候
her summer job at Harold Washington Library,
安德鲁高中上课的时候
classes at Andrews High School,
杰弗森小学  所有她可能见过他们的地方
Jefferson Elementary-- all places she potentially met them.
好  追踪下去
All right, good, chase that.
但别太钻牛角尖
but let's not get tunnel vision.
仍有可能汉娜在他们带走她之前
It's still possible Hannah didn't know these men well
并不怎么认识他们
before they took her.
等等  你还想我们像查绑架案那样查这案子吗
Wait, you still want us running this like it's an abduction?
我只想查得更宽泛些
I just wanna run wide.
她参与了
She participated.
过来
Come over here.
告诉我
Tell me something.
你看来这是自愿参与吗
That look like willing participation to you?
看上去是个吓坏了的孩子
All right, it looks like a scared kid.
但她仍然站着
But it also looks like a girl who stood two feet
站在门口七分钟
from an open door for seven minutes.
拿着武器
Who held a weapon.
本可以逃跑  大喊求救  但她没有
Could have ran, screamed for help, but she didn't.
是  当她走进警局的时候就是在求助了
Yeah, she asked for help when she walked in this district.
我们没有帮她
And we didn't give it to her.
查得快点  广泛点
I want it run fast and wide.
你知道那是谁  是吗
You know who that is, right?
是的
Yep.
那是你的朋友
That's your friend.
是汉娜
That's Hannah.
是吗
Right?
汉娜
Hannah.
他们是谁
Who are they?
这是你的朋友
This is your friend.
他们是谁
Who are they?
我不知道
I have no idea.
不知道
No idea?
你知道我能把你留在这里多久吗
You know how long I can keep you here?
我可以保证你再也离开不了
I can make sure you never leave.
我可以让你生不如死
I can make your life hell.
你还有大把日子要过
And you still got a lot of life left to live.
他帮不了你
He can't help you.
他为我工作
He works for me.
我可以大做文章的  艾迪
I can make this a lot of things, Addie.
妨碍司法公正  共谋
Obstruction of justice, conspiracy,
谋杀案的帮凶
accomplice to murder.
-但我没做  -因为我已经能
- But I didn't-- - 'Cause I can already
证明你向我撒谎了  艾迪
prove you're lying to me, Addie.
我也可以以那个罪名起诉你
I can charge you for that too
但我们现在说的是在一场银行劫案中杀死的三个钟
but we're talking about three homicides during a bank robbery--
-但我不在那  -所以你是
- But I wasn't there! - And that makes you
从犯  会受到联邦指控
an accessory, which comes with federal charges.
-不是的  简直疯了  -那是死刑
- No, that's insane! - And that is the death penalty.
但我什么都没做
But I'm not doing anything.
你会让你的朋友被杀的
You're getting your friend killed!
好
Okay.
这两个中高一点的那个叫迈克
The taller of the two's name is Mike.
好
Okay.
另一个叫"TT"
But the other one goes by the name of "TT."
我不知道他们姓什么
I don't know their last names.
但是迈克是汉娜的男朋友
But Mike's... Hannah's boyfriend.
男朋友还是皮条客
Boyfriend or pimp?
告诉我  我是说  他抓着她
Tell me. I mean, he's holding her.
逼她
Running her?
他伤害她吗
Does he hurt her?
迈克不伤害她  他...
Mike doesn't hurt her, he...
他爱她
He loves her.
她爱他
And she loves him.
如果她这么做的话  只是...
If she's doing this, it is only...
因为他这么做
because he is.
我相信你
I believe you.
好了  艾迪只知道迈克和TT
All right, all Addie knows is Mike and TT.
她不知道姓什么
She doesn't know their last names,
没去过他们的公寓  什么都不知道
never been to their apartments, nothing.
TT有很多纹身
TT's got a bunch of tattoos.
迈克的口音像是芝加哥的
Mike sounds like he's from Chicago.
好了  他们是暴力的人
All right, well, these are violent men.
假设他们过着暴力的生活
Let's assume they live violent lives.
该死  犯罪数据库里有3276个迈克
Damn, I got 3,276 Mikes in this criminal database.
好  民防处估计迈克身高1米85
Okay, well, the OCD tech estimated Mike's height at 6'1",
180斤  棕色眼睛
weight 180. Eye color brown.
-有用吗  -没多大用
- Does that help? - Nah, not really.
缩小了些范围
I mean, it trims it down a little bit,
但还是范围太大了
but it's still too wide for me.
年龄估计在32到36岁之间
Age was estimated 32 to 36.
一开始的抢劫案中的巡游者
Hey, the Land Cruiser that was used in the initial robbery
是从蓝岛的居民车库里偷的
was stolen from a residential garage in Blue Island.
主人说你从街上是看不到车库的
The owner says you couldn't see the garage from the street.
可能是某个当地的  说话带着芝加哥口音的人
Could be someone local, talks like Chicago.
好  好  蓝岛
Okay, okay. Copy Blue Island,
现在在蓝岛周围五英里我们有84个迈克
Now we have 84 with a five mile parameter around Blue Island.
大家伙  我们还需要在缩小点范围
Guys, we still need to narrow it down more.
有和监狱里外号叫"TT"的人有交集的吗
Any crosses with "TT" in the jail nickname system?
有很多  但是那84个人里没有
We've got tons of those, but nothing that run up against that 84.
纹身呢
What about tattoos?
等等
Hold up.
有7个
We got seven.
找到了  好...
Yep, got his ass. Okay...
特伦特·塔格蒂
看  特伦特·塔格蒂  33岁
Look at that, Trent Tagerty, 33 years old,
脖子上有T的纹身
tattoos of the T's on his neck.
他和迈克·谢菲尔德在联邦监狱里蹲过一年
He did a year with Mike Sheffield at MCC.
迈克·谢菲尔德因
Mike Sheffield was pinched
持械袭击和抢劫未遂被捕
for armed assault and attempted robbery.
好  把那些照片打出来
All right, print those pictures.
让艾迪确认一下
Get a confirmation from Addie.
他们都没有最近住址
Yeah, and neither has a last known address.
现在到处都有汉娜的照片信息和他们的录像
Hannah's ID is everywhere, the footage of them--
他们不可能走在大街上
They can't be out on the street.
他们会去他们认识的  信任的人那里
They'll go to someone they know, trust.
以前帮过他们的人
Someone that's helped them before.
特伦特·塔格蒂有个表哥
Trent Tagerty has a cousin.
沃伦·塔格蒂
沃伦  42岁
Warren, he's 42 years old,
在卡纳里维尔租了间公寓
rents an apartment in Canaryville.
他保释了特伦特四次  并是他的担保人
He's posted bond for Trent four times and has an open warrant.
好  准备好  我们去找他
All right, gear up. Let's hit it.
亚当
Adam.
听着  我想让你去一下欧沙家
Listen, I want you to hang back and swing by Osha's house.
等等  认真的吗  你想让我去他家
Wait, seriously, you want me to go to his house?
就告诉他我让你去的
Look, just tell him I sent you.
我知道他  他是个正直的人
I know him. He's a stand up guy.
说他想在哪里见面都可以  我们私下谈谈
Say I'll meet him anywhere he wants; we'll talk in private.
但是要现在
But it's gotta be now.
好吗  我不想再给他打电话了
Okay? I am done calling his ass.
去吧
Go.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
-去找那个女孩  -别动
- Hey, get the girl. - Hey, don't move!
-下床  快点  -安全
- Get out the bed, come on. - Clear!
下床  快点
Get your arms off the bed! Come on!
他不在这里  刚走
He ain't here. You just missed him.
趴到地上
Get on the floor!
楼下有个车库  他把我的车开走了
There's a garage downstairs. He took my car.
应该是五分钟之前
Had to be five minutes ago.
拜托  他不在这里
Please, he ain't here.
他在哪里
Where is he?
手举起来靠墙
Get your hands against the wall!
-你听到了  去车库  -快点  面朝墙
- You heard him. Hit that garage! - Hurry up! Against the wall!
-你没事吧  海莉  -没事
- You good, Hailey? - Good.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
迈克和汉娜在哪里
Where's Mike and Hannah?
他们在哪里
Where are they?
没人  汉娜不在这里
It's clear. Hannah's not here.
接下去是这样
So, here's what's going to happen.
我们在你表弟的住处找到一把枪
We recovered a gun in your cousin's apartment,
跟第一场抢劫案的弹道报告吻合
matches ballistics for the first robbery.
你包里的现金绑带
Cash in your duffle
跟货币兑换点的现金绑带一样
has got the same bands as the currency exchange.
知道我是什么意思了吗
See where I'm going with this?
你就站在鬼门关前面
You're starting out six feet under
而我们掌握了你的生死
and we got you dead to rights.
所以  你跟我们说的任何事
So, anything you tell us,
你帮我们找到他们而做的任何事
any way that you help us find them,
都会帮你一步一步远离鬼门关
it's gonna dig you a little above ground.
你这么想让我说吗
You want me to talk so bad?
给我找个律师  再给我一个辩诉协议
Get me a lawyer and get me a deal.
好的
Okay.
所以你想要辩诉协议
So you want a deal, huh?
你想要辩诉协议  好的  那...
You want a deal? Okay, so--
辩诉协议就是...
The deal is...
你开口
You're gonna talk.
你明白吗
You understand?
-现在你明白了吗  -明白  我明白了
- You understand now? - Yeah, yeah I do.
-我明白  -好
- I understand. - Okay.
很好
Good.
他们在哪里
Where are they?
-我不知道  -你不知道吗
- I don't know. - You don't know?
我不知道他们去哪里了
I don't know where they went.
好吧
Come on.
你最后一次看到他们是在哪里
Where did you last see them?
在第三十大街上狂奔
Running like hell down 30th street.
我不知道他们要去哪里  我发誓
I don't know where they were going, I swear.
原来的计划不是这样的
It wasn't supposed to go down like this.
抢两个地方  分三路跑
Two robberies, split three ways.
计划就这样  这么简单
That was the plan. It was easy.
结果迈克突然开始开枪
And then Mike just starts shooting
新闻上面全都是录像
and there's the footage all over the news.
汉娜的照片  我知道我们必须得逃
Hannah's picture-- I knew we had to get out.
我想说服她跟我走
I tried to convince her to come with me.
但她不肯离开他  她觉得这才是爱
And she wouldn't leave him. She thinks that's love.
谢谢  你去了吗
Thanks. You swing by?
他把我赶走了
He waved me off.
-你跟他说了是我让你去的吗  -说了
- You told him I sent you? - I did.
他跟我说你这是浪费时间
He told me that you're wasting your time.
你已经深陷其中了
And that he can't help you get in front of something
他没法帮你脱身
that you're already in the middle of.
这个迈克  是个人物
Then this Mike, he's quite a guy.
他整个人生都在各种机构
He spent more of his life inside institutions
进进出出
then out of them.
他在芝加哥还有几个家人
He's got a few family members still in Chicago.
我在信息联结网里查过
I ran them through Lexus Nexus.
他大概还有七个可能的藏身处
He's got about seven addresses he could be hiding out at.
各小组已经在路上了  警长
Got teams en route, Sarge.
交通组也公布了  马路  巴士  机场
Transport teams posted up too--Midway, Greyhound, O'Hare.
如果他们想离开这里  我们也会知道
They try to leave the city, we'll know about it.
特伦特说他们是步行
Trent said they were on foot,
所以他们会随时停下
so they're gonna get spotted eventually.
他们还会继续走
They'll trip up.
我们要赶在他们之前找到他们
Well, how about we find them before they do, hmm?
我刚跟...
I was just speaking to--
这个可能性我们一定要阻止
A possibility that we're gonna prevent.
好吗
Okay?
我们先一步找到他们  第一个到达现场
We're gonna find them first, so we're on the scene first,
然后安安静静地带他们回来
and we're gonna bring them in quiet.
很有可能  汉娜有武器
Chances are, Hannah's gonna be armed.
她之前有枪
She held a gun before.
可能没法安静地抓到他们
This might not be a quiet arrest.
我知道你很内疚  因为你给了她你的名片
Look, I know you feel guilty because you gave her your card.
我没有给她名片
I didn't give her my card.
我妻子给的
My wife did.
所以每个他们可能去的地方我们都去一遍
So let's hit every address they could run to.
试试所有的旅馆  招待所  收容所
Try every hotel, pay by night, hostel.
这点时间他们不会跑得太远
They haven't had time to run far.
快点找到他们
Let's find them.
你是要去那个地方吗
You going where I think you're going?
不好意思  先生  先生  你不能进去
Excuse me, sir? Sir, you cannot go in there.
先生  先生
Sir, sir!
你什么情况  吉姆
What's the matter with you, Jim?
汉克  你干什么
Hank, what are you doing?
现在不是时候
This is not the time to be doing this.
-你不接我的电话  -你赶紧出去
- You ignore my calls. - You need to walk out the door.
我打电话给你求助
I called and asked for help.
-汉克  你马上走  -你欠我的
- Hank, you need to leave now. - You owe me!
别  让他留下
No, let him stick around.
他  我们没事  汉克正准备走
He's--we're good. Hank was just leaving.
是吗  我觉得不是吧
Yeah, well, I don't believe that.
不过继续啊
But go right ahead.
所有这些  他在法庭上都用得上
All of this, he can use in court.
恐吓检察官
Intimidating a prosecutor.
所以  你想留下来看看大陪审团的审核吗
So, you wanna stay for the grand jury review?
好了  好了  不能这样
All right, all right, we're not doing this.
你想整垮我  丹尼  那就整我啊
You wanna tear me down, Denny, tear me down.
-但你别碰老埃  -我知道
- But you got no stake in Al. - Oh, I know that.
但老埃有你这个搭档  本来就
But Al's had the poor fortune of having had you
-没什么前途  -整我啊
- as his partner. - Tear me down!
-够了  -你想让他站在证人席上吗
- Enough! - You want him on the stand?
-我说够了  -冲我来
- Come on, I said enough! - Come at me!
-继续认罪  汉克  -这里不行
- Go ahead and confess, Hank. - Not here.
-走吧  -认罪吧  汉克
- Walk away. - Confess, Hank.
-汉克  -这份工作做了27年
- Hank. - 27 years on this job
我们都知道你手上不干净
and we both know that you did not do it clean.
子弹终于冲着你来了  汉克
Well, the bullet is finally coming for you, Hank.
只不过会先穿过奥林斯基
Just has to go through Olinsky first.
不不不  别这样  汉克  算了
No, no, no, no. Come on, Hank, let's go.
算了  算了
Let it go. Let it go.
-警长  -你来这里干什么
- Sarge. - Man, what are you doing here?
老埃让我来找你
Al asked me to check in on you.
你觉得呢我需要一个保姆吗
You think I need a babysitter?
做好你该做的事  亚当
Just do your damn job, Adam.
老大  我一直在给你打电话  但你手机关机了
Boss, I've been trying to call you but your phone's been off.
杰克逊的一家车行认出新闻上的人了
Car lot on Jackson recognized photos from the news.
三十多岁西班牙裔男性和一名深色头发少女一起
Male, Hispanic, 30s, and a teenage female with dark hair.
他们是去租车的
They came in looking for a car.
我们走
Let's go.
有枪
Gun!
找掩体
Cover!
等等  等等  等等
Hold on! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
上
Go!
-杰  你没事吧  -我没事
- Jay, you good? - Yeah, I'm good.
5021G  呼叫指挥部  有人持械袭警
5021 George, 10-1, 10-1. Shots fired at the police.
收到  5021G
Copy that, 5021 George.
里面没有别人了
There's no one else inside.
有两个出口  前面一个后面一个
There's two exits, one in front and one in back.
-有提出什么要求吗  -没有
- Any demands? - They don't have any.
我们能接通里面的电话  但是他们不接
Now, we have access to the landline but they won't answer.
没和我们说过话
Haven't said a word to us.
在前门对他们用无线电广播通讯
All right, start a line of communication at the front.
我从后门进去
I'll move up through the back.
警长  他们都持有武器
Sarge, they're both armed--
进行无线电广播通讯
Start a line of communication at the front.
迈克·谢菲尔德  我是芝加哥警察局的
Mike Sheffield, this is Antonio Dawson
安东尼奥·道森
of the Chicago Police Department.
我是来帮助你们的
I'm here to help you.
我只是想确保你们
I just wanna make sure all of us
都能平安离开这里
walk away from this safely.
大家都能平安无事
Everybody gets out of here unharmed.
也就是说  我是站在你们这边的
So that means, I'm the guy on your side.
你们可以告诉我
I'm the guy you talk to.
-我要自己进去  -我要知道...
- I'm going in alone. - I need to know...
你们想要什么  迈克
what we're looking at here, Mike.
我要怎么安全把你和汉娜救出来
How do I get you and Hannah out of here safely?
迈克  你在听吗  迈克
Mike? You listening, Mike?
迈克
Mike?
我会解决的  我会解决的
I'm gonna take care of it. I'll always take care of it.
没事的  你看到后面那扇门了吗
It's fine. Do you see a door back there?
-宝贝  你看到门了吗  -我没看到
- Look, baby, do you see a door? - I don't see any.
不  没事的  没事的
No, okay, that's okay.
他们不会进来的
All right, they're not coming in.
他们不会进来的  你知道为什么吗
They're not coming in, you know why, you know why?
因为我们能逃出去  我们能一起逃出去
Because we're going out. We're going to go all out.
我这样做都是为了我们
All right, I did all of this for us.
我有计划  我有计划  我们得...
All right, I got a plan. I got a plan, we're gonna--
你离我们远一点
Hey, hey, hey, hey! You stay away from us
-不然我把你的头打爆  -冷静点
- or I'll shoot your head off! - Take it easy.
冷静点
Take it easy!
Take it easy.
如果你开枪  这扇门就会被冲破
Look, you fire one shot, that door gets busted down
你们都得死  冷静点
and you are both dead, so just take it easy.
听着  冷静点
Hey. Look, take it easy.
好吗
Okay?
-安东尼奥  我进来了  -收到
- Antonio, I'm inside. - Copy that.
迈克  放下武器
Mike, put your weapon down.
放下你的武器  踢过来
Just put your weapon down, kick it over here,
我们可以好好谈谈
and we can have a conversation.
你们让我进去  我们能谈谈
You do that, I can come in there, we can talk.
我们可以想个办法
Hey, we can figure a way out of this.
迈克  外面有几十个警察
Mike, there are dozens of cops out there.
所有出口都有人把守
All the exits are covered.
你们不能拿着枪走出去
You can't walk outside armed.
你们一出门就会没命的
You will be dead before you hit the ground.
-听着  -不  汉娜
- Okay, listen-- - No, Hannah,
汉娜  听我说
Hannah, listen to me.
汉娜  你找我帮忙  我还是能帮你
Hannah, you came to me for help--I can still help you.
-我会帮你  -听着  我很抱歉
- I'm gonna help you. - Look, I'm sorry
前几年我都没在你的身边
I wasn't there for you the last few years.
我知道迈克一直陪着你
And I know Mike was.
我明白  你不想失去他
Look, I get it. You don't want to lose him,
我明白
I understand.
但他带你走向了歧途  汉娜  这不是你
But he led you wrong, Hannah. This is not you.
汉娜  你不用走上这条路
Hannah, you don't have to go out this way.
-现在还有时间  -听我数三
- There's still time. - On three.
不  迈克  别带她出去
No, Mike! Do not take her out of there!
别带她出去
Do not make her go out there!
-不  -持枪
- No! - Gun!
放下武器
Drop your weapon!
-不要开火  -上
- Stand down! - Move in!
不要开火  不要开火
Stand down, stand down!
警察出来了
Police, coming out!
天啊
Oh, my God.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
卡米尔曾经是汉娜的老师
Camille was Hannah's teacher?
一年级
First grade.
是的  卡米尔...卡米尔很爱她
Yeah, Camille-- Camille loved her.
她经常回家说她的故事
I mean, she always came home with stories about her.
说她是个"小祸害"
How she was "A menace."
"噩梦"
"A nightmare."
卡米尔很照顾她
Camille really looked out for her.
她病了以后就由我来照顾她了
She got sick, I took over.
我每年都会去看汉娜  直到贾斯汀死了
I checked in on Hannah every year until--until Justin died.
我...
I just...
忘了
Forgot.
我没在她身边
I wasn't there for her.
是别人陪着她
Someone else was.
你救不了所有人  汉克
You can't save everyone, Hank.